Data set:
	SMOS
Description: 
	High school student monitoring system
Source: 
	Use cases 
Target: 
	Classes

Directory structure
	all_req_filenames.txt: source artifacts file (67 artifacts)
	all_code_filenames: target artifacts file (100 artifacts)
	UC2CC.csv: answer matrix file (1044 links)
	req: directory that contains actual source artifacts
	code: directory that contains actual target artifacts
	

Original data source: 
	M. Gethers, R. Oliveto, D. Poshyvanyk, and A. D.Lucia. 
	On integrating orthogonal information retrieval methods to improve traceability recovery. 
	In Proc. of Intn’l Conf. on Software Maintenance, 2011.
	
Translated data source:
	Improving Traceability Link Recovery Using Fine-grained Requirements-to-Code Relations.